A Guide to the School of Education/VSU- Record Group 1927-
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Correspondence
  - By subject heading
    - Survey of Higher Education n.d. (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Survey of Higher Education n.d. (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Teachers Pageant n.d. (Box-folder 24:12)
    - The Theatre-Guild 1959-1966 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Tuberculosis Correspondence 1936-1945 (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Tuberculosis Correspondence 1946-1949 (Box-folder 24:15)
    - Tuberculosis-Minutes, by-laws, newsletters n.d. (Box-folder 24:16)
    - Tuberculosis Printed n.d. (Box-folder 24:17)
    - Training Schools-Blanford-Matoaca n.d. (Box-folder 24:18)
    - Unit Teaching-Care of Teeth 1937 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - The Virginia Conference on Family Relations 1940-1945 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - The Virginia Conference on Family Relations 1946-1949 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - The Virginia Conference on Family Relations-Minutes, Programs n.d. (Box-folder 25:4)
    - The Virginia Conference on Family Relations printed n.d. (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Virginia State High School n.d. (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Virginia State High School n.d. (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Virginia State High School- weekly Teachers Bulletin 1935 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Virginia Associations Correspondence 1944-1946 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Virginia Teachers Association 1942-1947 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - The Virginia Teachers Association 1948-1951 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Virginia Committee to Study History 1948-1949 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Virginia Committee to Study History 1949 (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Virginia society for Research Correspondence-Minutes 1931-1944 (Box-folder 25:14)
    - VSU Credit Union n.d. (Box-folder 25:15)
    - Program War Needs 1943 (Box-folder 25:16)
    - Educational Workshop/Reports, Minutes n.d. (Box-folder 25:17)
    - Educational Workshop Jan-June 1941 (Box-folder 25:18)
    - Educational Workshop Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 25:19)
    - Workshop Educational 1945 (Box-folder 25:20)
    - Educational Workshop 1942-1949 (Box-folder 25:21)
    - Workshop(Charlotte County) 1943 (Box-folder 25:22)
    - Worshop(Charlotte County) 1943 (Box-folder 25:23)
  - Correspondence by Alphabet
    - A-Correspondence 1946, 1950 (Box-folder 26:1)
    - A-Correspondence 1953 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Correspondence-B 1920-1935 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Correspondence-B 1936-1941 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - General Correspondence B 1942-1944 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - General Correspondence B 1942-1944 (Box-folder 26:6)
    - General Correspondence B 1952-1953 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - General Correspondence B 1937-1943 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - General Correspondence B 1944-1947 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - General Correspondence B 1950-1953 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - General Correspondence B 1941-1948 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - General Correspondence -D 1935-1937 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - General Correspondence -D(Department Reports) 1939-1942 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - General Correspondence -D 1943-1952 (Box-folder 26:14)
    - E-Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 26:15)
    - F- Correspondence 1944-1953 (Box-folder 26:16)
    - F-Fz Programs n.d. (Box-folder 26:17)
    - General Correspondence H 1936-1949 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - General Correspondence H 1950-1952 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - J-K 1937-1947 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - K 1943, 1951 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - L 1941-1950 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - M 1942-1952 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - General Correspondence P 1942-1951 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - General Correspondence P 1952 (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Q 1936-1952 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - R 1940-1948 (Box-folder 27:10)
    - R 1951 (Box-folder 27:11)
    - R 1952-1953 (Box-folder 27:12)
    - S 1942-1952 (Box-folder 27:13)
    - T n.d. (Box-folder 27:14)
    - V n.d. (Box-folder 27:15)
    - General Correspondence 1937-1952 (Box-folder 27:16)
    - General Correspondence (YMCA) 1945 (Box-folder 27:17)